{"data":[{"question":"The new musical has taken theatre audiences throughout the country with storm.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"musical","b":"audiences","c":"throughout","d":"with","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Musical-> music","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"There's quiet a lot of criticism directed at the police nowadays.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"There's","b":"quiet","c":"criticism","d":"directed","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Quiet-> quite","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"She has a good commands of spoken English.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has","b":"good","c":"commands","d":"spoken","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Commands-> command","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Her reaction where she finally found her brother was one of disbelief.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"where","b":"finally","c":"found","d":"was","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Where-> when","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"As the teacher talked to us, I pretended to drop a pencil and bent over.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"As","b":"talked","c":"pretended","d":"bent over","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Talked-> was talking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"I am very glad that you have chosen for me.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"very","b":"that","c":"have chosen","d":"for","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- For-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"I am afraid that I am unable accepting the offer.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"afraid","b":"that","c":"unable","d":"accepting","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Accepting-> to accept","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"I shall be take up a similar position with another company soon.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"take up","b":"position","c":"another","d":"soon","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Take up-> taken up","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"As pay and conditions are gooder there I am turning down your offer.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"conditions","b":"gooder","c":"there","d":"down","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Gooder -> better","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"},{"question":"Thank you for the time what you gave to my application.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"for","b":"time","c":"what","d":"to","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- What-> that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"20","type":"1"}]}